internationalman.com 2013-12-25

# Casey Research, LLC Privacy Policy | Casey Research

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites (together, the "Sites") that are owned or operated by Casey Research, LLC (referred to herein as "we," "us," and "our"), including CaseyResearch.com, KitcoCasey.com and any other websites that display or link to this Privacy Policy. We collect certain personal information based upon and as a result of the use of our Sites by visitors and subscribers (referred to herein as "you" or "your"). Our collection and use of your information will be conducted in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**1\. Information That We Collect.**

When you subscribe to our products and services, you disclose and we collect certain personal information from you, such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number or fax number, username, password, credit card number, and other information described in this Privacy Policy ("Personal Information"). We also automatically collect anonymous tracking information about you to gauge response to our communication efforts and the popularity of specific areas of our Sites.

Our Sites use cookies, which are small files placed on your computer’s hard drive by an Internet server when you visit a website. We use cookies to allow authentication for access to subscriber-only areas of our Sites and to assure that the content you view is appropriate to your subscription status. Cookies also allow you to leave our Sites and come back without having to re-enter your username and password every time (within a limited time period). If you do not want to accept cookies from our Sites, you may configure your web browser so that it does not accept cookies; however, certain functions available on the website may be lost.

**2\. Consent.**

By providing your Personal Information through the Sites, you consent to our collection and use of your Personal Information and other information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Our Use of Your Personal Information.**

 **a.** We will use your Personal Information to process your subscription or requests for information. We may also use such Personal Information to offer additional information to you about us, our products and/or services, personalize the types of information you receive from us, evaluate how our Sites are being used and the audience our Sites are reaching, identify market trends and market interests that help us improve the products and services that we offer, and develop and improve the content and operation of our Sites to better serve the needs of our customers.

(1) 

_Online Orders_

. When you purchase a subscription from us, we will request certain Personal Information, including credit card information. Individuals who do not have a Visa, MasterCard or American Express credit card are not permitted to make purchases with us online.

(2) 

_Sharing Information with Other Companies_

. We may share your Personal Information ( **but never your credit card or password information)** with our affiliates or with third parties who provide services to us and agree to keep your Personal Information confidential.

(3) 

_Mailing and Email Addresses_

. We will use your mailing and email addresses to send you the publications you have subscribed to. We may also contact you with questions about your subscription or service, or to remind you of your password, if necessary. If you submit an inquiry via email about one of your subscriptions, for security reasons we may ask you to provide additional information so we can verify your identity.

**b.** We may send you information and special offers on our other products. We may also, on occasion, use your mailing or email address to send you information or special offers from select companies that offer products, services or information we believe may be of interest to you. Though we hope you gain value from the email messages you receive, you can choose to opt out of receiving further messages by following the instructions provided at the bottom of each email.

You may, at any time, request to not have your mail and email information used for information and offers from us or other companies by contacting our customer service center at 1-888-512-2739 (1-602-445-2736 if calling internationally) or [opt-out@caseyresearch.com](mailto:opt-out@caseyresearch.com).

**c.** We will only disclose your Personal Information to our employees, affiliates, agents, contractors, or other third parties who have a need to know such information for the uses listed above. Except as provided above, we will not disclose Personal Information to any other third parties.

**d.** Personal Information may also be aggregated with such information from other visitors to the Sites such that the information no longer personally identifies you. We may use the aggregated information for the general purpose of evaluating our market and/or business trends, our customer demographics, interests and behavior, our past and future product or service offerings and/or pricing, or other aspects of our business. We may share such aggregated information with our business partners, vendors, distributors or other collaborators, for these same purposes. We may also sell or license such aggregate information to one or more third parties for use in a similar manner.

**e.** We also retain the right to release your Personal Information when required by law or when we, in good faith, believe that we must release the information in order to: (1) satisfy a legal order or comply with legal process; (2) defend our rights or those of our affiliates or business partners; or (3) protect the personal safety of our employees, agents, affiliates, business partners, customers, or site users. We also retain the right to transfer your Personal Information in the context of the sale of all or part of our business.

**4\. Security.**

Although we take the security of your Personal Information very seriously and are constantly improving our efforts to protect it, no electronic communication over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secured. Though we take great care to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you submit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**5\. Advertising and Linked Websites.**

Our Sites may feature products and services that are co-sponsored by other websites. One example of such a feature is our stock quote data, which is provided to us by a third party. Additionally, our Sites contain links to other websites, including those of advertisers. We are not responsible for the claims or representations made by advertisers or sponsors. While these co-sponsored activities, banner ads, and links originate on our Sites, we do not necessarily operate them.

For example, if you click on a link or banner advertisement, you’ll be directed to the advertiser’s site. These other sites may use cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. Since we do not have control over the privacy practices or the content of these sites, we recommend that you check their privacy policies before giving out any personal information. We do not own, control, have access to, or maintain any information collected by our co-sponsors or advertisers. Some e-letter issues also include advertising. By opting to receive e-letters from Casey Research, you also agree to receive such advertisements.

**6\. Changes to Privacy Policy.**

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your Personal Information, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. You should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a notice on the Sites and by sending a notice to you via email to your last email address in our records.

Please note that you are responsible for updating your personal information with us, including any changes to your email address. In the event that the last email address you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our sending of the email containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.

**7\. Contacting Us.**

You may contact us regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting our customer service center at 1-888-512-2739 (1-602-445-2736 if calling internationally) or by writing to PO Box 84900, Phoenix, AZ 85071.

**_Effective as of December 1, 2008._**
